http://wiccanspirituality.com/privacy-policy.html

Wicca Spirituality with erin Dragonsong
A New Wicca for a New World
Menu
*WICCA SCHOOL*Wicca SchoolA Year & A Day: Wiccan e-courseBook of ShadowsBook of MirrorsWhat Students Say about A Year & A Day!
BeginnersBeginning WiccaWiccan HolidaysChristianity & WiccaFAQsWiccan SymbolsStarting Your Book of Shadows
Being a WitchBeing A WitchWiccan InfoGender in WiccaFinding Wiccan NameWiccan MusicGods & GoddessesPower of the Moon
MagickWiccan MagickWiccan Altar & ToolsWiccan PracticesWiccan RitualDivinationCreative VisualizationPowers of Pagan Jewellery
Wiccan SuppliesErin's ExclusivesYule Songs & Carols
SpiritualityWicca SpiritualitySelf-HealingSpiritual Practices & Power ToolsDream WorkMandalas as a Spiritual Practice
Great Planetary HealingRebirth of the Goddess!The Great Spiritual RebirthShift of AgesSurviving the Planetary TransitionLife in the New ParadigmModern Shamans & SensitivesEnergy-Protection for Highly Sensitive People
AboutEnergy ExchangeAbout erinEmailTestimonialsPsychicReadings
300+ ArticlesWicca Spirituality Library: Your Access to Tons of Free InfoSiteMap (Table of Contents)BlogSilver Chalice Wiccan Email MagazineAnimal Spirit GuidesMiracles ArchiveSamhain Celebration
Wicca-Spirituality.com's Privacy Policy
I understand that you, like me, care deeply about what information is gathered and how it is used, and I appreciate your trust that I will do so carefully, sensibly, and responsibly.
The information I learn from customers and subscribers helps me personalise and continually improve your experience at Wicca-Spirituality.com.
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Wicca-Spirituality.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.
Wicca-Spirituality.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations.
Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
Personal Information
Wicca-Spirituality.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, and used to improve the content of our website, notify you of updates, and respond to your inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, we discard it or store it in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not ever be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our system to recognize your browser.
The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have come to the site for the first time, or have returned to a specific page. If you personalize the site's pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Wicca-Spirituality.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying settings in your browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. Beacons are also referred to as web bugs. They are commonly used by sites that use third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a website.
As you browse this website, Google Analytics and advertising cookies will be placed on your computer to collect demographic and interest information, but we do not tie the cookie to any personal information that you provide to us. If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you may use their opt-out tool... https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.
Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads. This cookie enables Google to serve ads to users based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions should not cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If Wicca-Spirituality.com is sold (FYI, never gonna happen!), the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records, or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.
Updates and Effective Date
Wicca-Spirituality.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to Wicca-Spirituality.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Thanks for taking the time to check out the security of your privacy!
With Brightest Blessings,
Email
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to send me a newsletter.
Subscribe
Follow @WiccaSpirit
Recent Articles
Samhain Journey Guided Visualization with erin Dragonsong Oct 22, 20 09:35 PMSamhain Journey Guided Visualization with erin Dragonsong Read More
My Patron Goddess is MA'AT Sep 27, 20 01:00 AMShe is the Ancient Egyptian Goddess of Justice, truth and Harmony, the personification of the cosmic order and a representation of the stability of the Read More
Kibele and Leto
Sep 27, 20 12:51 AMKibele
because is the bountiful earth mother, the first and the last. She is the all mighty.
Leto because she is the mother of twins Artemis and Apollo, Read More
[?]Subscribe To This Site
Wicca Spirituality™ By erin Dragonsong
Founder & CES
(Chief Esoteric Scientist)
Copyright © 2006 - 2020 Wicca-Spirituality.com™
Note: "Wicca Spirituality" is a copyrighted name for a specific Wiccan tradition, not to be confused with "Wiccan Spirituality"
All Rights Reserved Worldwide.
Copyright protected by law and karma.
SBI!
